Class of 1903 Records, 1899-1970
Smith College Archives
Class of 1903 Records
1899-1970
Smith College. Class of 1903.
RG 80 UUID:2f7006a7-120a-4a9f-8200-58c570814ecd
19 boxes (10.6 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 19 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1903.
The Class of 1903 was the twenty-fifth entering class and the twenty-fifth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1903 records, 1899-1970, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1903, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, minutes, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1903 records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Baccalaureate Service 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 2)
- Commencement Music 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 3)
- Commencement Speaker 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 4)
- Freshman Frolic given by 1902 1899 (Box 1630, Folder 5)
- Freshman Grind by 1902 1899 (Box 1630, Folder 6)
- Freshman Handbook 1899 (Box 1630, Folder 7)
- Gifts 1918, 1967 (Box 1630, Folder 8)
- Granddaughters and Great-Granddaughter 1965-1968 (Box 1630, Folder 9)
- Groups-Photographs 1899-1903 (Box 1630, Folder 10)
- History undated (Box 1630, Folder 11)
- Ivy Day 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 12)
- Ivy Day Photographs 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 13)
- Jabberwock Block Print 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 14)
- Junior Frolic 1902 (Box 1630, Folder 15)
- Junior Prom 1902 (Box 1630, Folder 16)
- Junior Prom-Garden Party 1902 (Box 1630, Folder 17)
- Junior-Senior Party given by Class of 1904 1903 (Box 1630, Folder 18)
- Junior Ushers 1902 (Box 1630, Folder 19)
- Class Letters 1939-1970 (Box 1630, Folder 20)
- Minutes 1899-1913 (Box 1631, Folder 1)
- Minutes 1899-1963 (Box 1631, Folder 2)
- President's Correspondence 1958-1968 (Box 1631, Folder 3)
- Promenade Concert 1903 (Box 1631, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1904 (Box 1631, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1906 (Box 1631, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1908 (Box 1631, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1913 (Box 1631, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1923 (Box 1631, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1928 (Box 1631, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1933 (Box 1631, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1938 (Box 1631, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1943 (Box 1631, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1948 (Box 1631, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1953 (Box 1631, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1958 (Box 1631, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1963 (Box 1631, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1968 (Box 1631, Folder 18)
- Reunion Publications 1913-1963 (Box 1631, Folder 19)
- Reunion Songs undated (Box 1631, Folder 20)
- Senior Dramatics 1903 (Box 1632, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1903 (Box 1632, Folder 2)
- Songs undated (Box 1632, Folder 3)
- Sophomore Reception 1901 (Box 1632, Folder 4)
- Class Supper 1903 (Box 1632, Folder 5)
- Scrapbook 1903-1922 (Box 1633, Folder 1)
- Alumnae Days 1923-1947 (Box 1633, Folder 2)
- Alumnae Days 1948-1964 (Box 1633, Folder 3)
- Class Secretary's Records-General 1903-1959 (Box 1634, Folder 1)
- Class Secretary's Records-Obituaries A-W (Box 1634, Folder 2)
- Class Secretary's Records-A-Be (Box 1634, Folder 3)
- Class Secretary's Records-Bl-Bu (Box 1634, Folder 4)
- Class Secretary's Records-C-Co (Box 1634, Folder 5)
- Class Secretary's Records-Cr-Dr (Box 1634, Folder 6)
- Class Secretary's Records-Du-E (Box 1634, Folder 7)
- Class Secretary's Records-F-Fr (Box 1634, Folder 8)
- Class Secretary's Records-Fu-Gi (Box 1634, Folder 9)
- Class Secretary's Records-Go-Gr (Box 1634, Folder 10)
- Class Secretary's Records-H-He (Box 1634, Folder 11)
- Class Secretary's Records-Hi-Ho (Box 1634, Folder 12)
- Class Secretary's Records-J-Ki (Box 1634, Folder 13)
- Class Secretary's Records-Kn-Ma (Box 1634, Folder 14)
- Class Secretary's Records-N-Po (Box 1635, Folder 1)
- Class Secretary's Records-McC-McN (Box 1635, Folder 2)
- Class Secretary's Records-Me-Mu (Box 1635, Folder 3)
- Class Secretary's Records-Pu-Ru (Box 1635, Folder 4)
- Class Secretary's Records-S-Sh (Box 1635, Folder 5)
- Class Secretary's Records-St-Su (Box 1635, Folder 6)
- Class Secretary's Records-T-Wa (Box 1635, Folder 7)
- Class Secretary's Records-We-Z (Box 1635, Folder 8)
- Reunion Memorabilia (Box OV)